wheretraveler.com 2019-06-08

# Privacy Policy - Morris Communications

* * *

### **Applicability and Preface**

This privacy policy is applicable to all internet sites, including mobile sites, to Morris Communications Company, LLC, and the below named subsidiaries (collectively, the “Morris Companies”, “We” or “Us”).

####  **Morris Companies:**

Morris Communications Company, LLC  
MCC Magazines, LLC  
Morris Visitor Publications, LLC  
Morris Business Media, LLC  
MVP Global, LLC

We are committed to protecting consumer privacy online. We believe that greater protection of personal privacy on the Web will not only protect consumers, but also increase consumer confidence and ultimately their participation in online activities. We intend to give you as much control as possible over your personal information. The purpose of our policy is to inform you about the types of information we gather about you when you visit our site(s), how we may use that information, whether we disclose it to anyone, and the choices you have regarding our use of, and your ability to correct, the information. Our site(s) may contain links to other Web sites, including Web sites directed to children. We have no control over the privacy practices or the content of any of our business partners, advertisers, sponsors or other sites to which we provide links from our sites. You should check the applicable privacy policy of the Web site sponsor when linking to other Web sites. We strive to offer their respective visitors the many advantages of Internet technology and to provide an interactive and personalized experience. We may use Personally Identifiable Information (your name, e-mail address, street address, telephone number and other information) subject to the terms of this privacy policy. Please note this policy applies only to information collected by us online and does not impact information collected or used by us or our affiliates through other means.

###  **How We gather information from Users**

How we collect and store information depends on the page you are visiting, the activities in which you elect to participate and the services provided. You can visit many pages on our site without providing any information. Other pages may prompt you to provide information, such as when you register for access to portions of our site, sign up for membership, request certain features (e.g., newsletters, news updates and other products), sign up for a magazine or newspaper subscription or make a purchase. You may also provide information when you participate in sweepstakes and contests, voting and polling activities, blogs, message boards and chat rooms and other interactive areas of our site. Like most Web site operators, we also collect information automatically and through the use of electronic tools that may be transparent to our visitors. For example, we may log the name of your Internet Service Provider or use ‘cookie’ technology. Among other things, the cookie may store your user name and password, sparing you from having to re-enter that information each time you visit, or may control the number of times you encounter a particular advertisement while visiting our site. As we adopt additional technology, we may also gather information through other means. In certain cases, you can choose not to provide us with information, for example by setting your browser to refuse to accept cookies, but doing so may limit your ability to access certain portions of the site. Additionally we may not be able to customize the site’s features according to your preferences.

###  **What We do with the information We collect**

We will use your information only as permitted by law. Aggregated Information (information that does not personally identify you) may be used in many ways. As one example, we may combine information about your usage patterns with similar information obtained from other users to learn which pages are visited most or what features are most attractive. Aggregated Information may occasionally be shared with our advertisers and business partners, but cannot be used to contact you individually.

We also collect information to enhance your visit and deliver more individualized content and advertising. For example, We may use Personally Identifiable Information collected on our sites to communicate with you regarding our Terms of Service and privacy policy, products and services offered by Us and our affiliates and partners, administration of sweepstakes and contests, processing e-commerce transactions and other topics We think you might find of interest. We reserve the right to share this information with certain of our affiliates and business units, including for example our affiliated publications and entities in which we have an ownership interest (collectively, ‘Affiliates’). This policy does not apply to any Affiliate’s use of such information.

Personally Identifiable Information collected by us may also be used for other purposes including but not limited to site administration and troubleshooting. Certain third parties who provide technical support for the operation of our site (our Web hosting service and our newsletter provider, for example) may access such information.

As we continue to develop our business, we may sell, buy, merge or partner with other companies or businesses. In such transactions, user information may be among the transferred assets. We may also disclose your information in response to a court order, at other times when we believe we are reasonably required to do so by law, in connection with the collection of amounts you may owe to us, and/or whenever we deem it appropriate or necessary to give such information to law enforcement authorities. Please note we may not provide you with notice prior to disclosure in such cases.

###  **Affiliated Sites, Linked Sites, and Advertisements**

We expect our partners, advertisers and third-party affiliates to respect the privacy of our users. However, third parties, including our partners, advertisers, affiliates and other content providers accessible through our site, may have their own privacy and data collection policies and practices. For example, during your visit to our site you may link to, or view as part of a frame on one of our pages, certain content that is actually created or hosted by a third party. Also, through our sites you may be introduced to, or be able to access, information, Web sites, advertisements, features, contests or sweepstakes offered by other parties. We are not responsible for the actions or policies of such third parties. You should check the applicable privacy policies of those third parties when providing information on a feature or page operated by a third party.

While on our site, our advertisers, promotional partners or other third parties may use cookies or other technology to attempt to identify some of your preferences or retrieve information about you. For example, some of our advertising is served by third parties and may include cookies that enable the advertiser to determine whether you have seen a particular advertisement before. Through features available on our site, third parties may use cookies or other technology to gather information. We do not control the use of this technology or the resulting information and is not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties.

Please be careful and responsible whenever you are online. Should you choose to voluntarily disclose Personally Identifiable Information on our site, such as in message boards, chat areas or in advertising or notices you post, that information can be viewed publicly and can be collected and used by third parties without our knowledge and may result in unsolicited messages from other individuals or third parties. Such activities are beyond the control of us and this policy.

We use the information we collect about you in the following ways:

  * To respond to any requests from you regarding sales and support.
  * To contact you regarding any agreements or accepted terms that you may have with us.
  * To provide you with marketing emails, special offers, advertising campaigns, or newsletters.
  * To provide you with information logs associated with the use of ours.
  * To contact you regarding functionality changes to our Services or website.
  * To develop new features and functionality to our Services and website.
  * To collect payment and bill for our Services.
  * To help personalize searches.
  * To diagnose problems.
  * To find and prevent fraud.
  * To register your domain and IP address through ARIN (American Registry for Internet Numbers).
  * To carry out other purposes as disclosed to you through the website, or found in terms or an agreement between you and the company or its subsidiaries.
  * Process for other purposes for which we obtain your consent.

###  **How we share your information**

  *  _Third Party Providers_ – We may share your information with third party providers that provide services on our behalf or resellers who provide us with services. These companies may assist with marketing support, processing credit card payments, content delivery, email, providing sales leads, and customer support. Third party providers may only process personal information pursuant to our instructions, and in compliance with this Privacy Policy and other applicable regulations.
  *  _Advertising_ – Based on the cookies and other tracking devices, we may work with advertising companies to display ads that may be of interest to you.
  *  _Business Transactions_ – To provide information to a third party in the event of any disposition of all or any portion of our business (e.g. reorganization, sale, assignment, bankruptcy).
  *  _Aggregated or De-identified Data_ – We may disclose or use aggregated or de-identified information with third party providers for research purposes relating to our Services.
  *  _As Required by Law or Similar Investigations_ – To comply with legal obligations (e.g. subpoena) or investigate potential legal violations. We may be required to share personal data in response to lawful requests from public authorities including to meet national security and/or law enforcement requirements.
  *  _Safety_ – We may disclose your information to protect and defend our in connection with investigating and preventing fraud or security issues.
  *  _Consent_ – We may also share your information with your consent.

###  **Your Choices**

  * You may unsubscribe from receiving promotional or marketing emails from us at any time by using the “unsubscribe” link in the email received, or by emailing us at [richard.brashear@morris.com](mailto:richard.brashear@morris.com).
  * You can also control your cookie settings.
  * With respect to your account information, you may update, correct or delete information that you provided to us by or contacting us at [richard.brashear@morris.com](mailto:richard.brashear@morris.com)

###  **Children**

We do not knowingly collect or solicit Personally Identifiable Information from or about children under the age of 13, except as permitted by law. If we discover we have received any information from a child under the age of 13 in violation of this policy, we will delete that information immediately. If you believe we have any information from or about anyone under the age of 13, please contact us at [ richard.brashear@morris.com.](mailto:webmaster@Wheretraveler.com)

###  **Compliance with legal process**

We may disclose personal information if We are required to do so by law or We in good faith believe that such action is necessary to (1) comply with the law or with legal process; (2) protect and defend our rights and property; (3) protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our websites; or (4) protect the personal safety or property of our users or the public (among other things, this means that if you provide false information or attempt to pose as someone else, information about you may be disclosed as part of any investigation into your actions).

###  **Data Subject Rights**

Individuals located in the European Union (“EU”) may have additional statutory rights available to them with respect to their personal information, including the right to access your personal information, have it erased, have it corrected, or object to or restrict processing. If you would like to make such a request, please email richard.brashear@morris.com. We will respond within thirty (30) days. We will need to verify that the individual is inquiring about his/her own information before we can assist with the request.

We will comply with such requests to the extent legally required by applicable law. For EU individuals, you also have the right to lodge a complaint with the supervisory authority.

###  **Changes to Privacy Policy**

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time, however, should we change the Privacy Policy in a material way, and a notice will be posted on our website along with the updated Privacy Policy. If you disagree with the changes, you may terminate your relationship with us, effective as of such date.

###  **How To Contact Us**

For any questions or comments, you may contact us:

  *  _ **By E-mail:**_ [richard.brashear@morris.com](mailto:richard.brashear@morris.com)
  *  _ **By Phone:**_ [800-680-4035](tel:1-800-680-4035) or [706-823-3200](tel:1-706-823-3200)
  *  _ **By Fax:**_ 706-836-3596
  *  _ **By Mail:**_ 643 Broad Street, Augusta GA 30901
